Curriculum vitae

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Abd Al-Rahman Al-Sahli



Erbil, Iraq

0750 609 8907

x abdalsahli.94@gmail.com

I am a highly organized and self-driven individual, passionate about developing my career in the field of Accounting. My commitment can be gauged from the fact that I am an accredited holder of a bachelor degree with Economic as specialization from Damascus university.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/02/2018-01/02/2020

Accountant

Cut for production and distribution (Damascus, Syria)

- Prepare journal entries on the Al-Amin program.
- Preparing bank reconciliations and monthly adjustments for all accounts in the financial statements.
- Prepare periodic (cash-payment-receipt) orders and verify them with the manager .
- Make estimated budgets and daily costs for work performed during the business year.
- Carrying out all administrative transactions related to the office at government departments

1/03/2017-31/10/2017

Inventory accountant

Bee Factory of patisserie (Syria)

- Prepare journal entries on the Al-Amin program.
- Preparing daily and monthly reports for all stores.
- Record each cost centre or production department with its withdrawals.
- Monitor inventory transactions.
- Taking payments from sales halls and comparing them with the accounts for each branch.
- Coordination with the cost accountant to ensure correctness of work.

01/01/2016-28/02/2017

Accountant

Ghazal & Anise Sanitary ware trading company (Syria)

- Prepare journal entries on AL- Ameen program.
- bills of sale and purchase
- Matching customer balances.
- Corresponded with clients, merchants and banks
- Produced action plans to resolve accounting problems

1/10/2014-30/09/2015

Casher

Plus restaurant (Syria)

- · receive customers' orders by phone
- Taking Payments
- Give accurate and appropriate information to answer customer's questions.
- Supervising on the work of employees in the hall.

1/07/2013-30/09/2014

Casher

Al Rawdah Super Market

- Taking payment, Doing Refunds
- Providing customer service, learning about the products and prices.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/03/2019-01/11/2019

Diploma in International Finance Reporting (dipifr) (in progress)

01/01/2019-01/10/2019

Integrated accounting centre, Damascus (Syria)

Diploma of Tourism Facilities Management. (80%)

01/01/2012-01/01/2018

Jiljamish Centre, Damascus (Syria)

Bachelor degree (BSc) in Economics, Banking and Insurance. (73.26%)

Damascus University, Damascus (Syria)

PERSONAL SKILLS

Mother tongue(s)

Arabic

Foreign language(s)

| UNDERSTANDING | | SPEAKING | | WRITING |
|---------------|---------|--------------------|-------------------|---------|
| Listening | Reading | Spoken interaction | Spoken production | |
| Good | Good | Good | Good | Good |

English

Communication skills

- Developed team work and collaborating skills.
- Established conflict management and resolution skills.
- Excellent presentation and negotiation skills.
- Self-motivated
- Working under pressure
- Good self-learning ability

Job-related skills

- Performing well under pressure.
- Exceptional organization and time management skills.
- Experience with accounting programs (Al-ameen, Al-edari,).

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Courses

Microsoft Office and ICDL, Excel For Accounting, Advanced Excel.

English Courses.

Accounting Programs.

Intermediate Accounting (IA).

Training course at customer service at The international bank for trade & finaiac.

Driving licence

B, Expiry date 04/2021